You didn't start your business to do
admin, but every week hours disappear into
invoicing, scheduling, client follow -ups and paperwork.
Sound familiar. Rizflow maps your workflows, finds
exactly where time and money leak and
builds custom AI agents that handle all
of it automatically. Your agents plug into
Slack, HubSpot, Telegram, Notion and 50 more
tools you already use. No rip and
replace. Go live in two to four
weeks, then it just runs. Admin, CAHM's,
Billing, Scheduling, 24 .7. You cut operating
costs by up to 60%. You reclaim
20 plus hours every week, and you
check everything from your phone in under
30 minutes. But we don't just handle
admin. Rizflow agents track inventory, manage supply
chains, and automate stock taking for trading
businesses, retail, F and B and logistics.
Real -time stock alerts, purchase order automation,
supplier coordination. Every unit accounted for every
reorder timed perfectly. Don't just take our
word for it. Rain fresh and e
-commerce brand came to us buried in
manual orders and stock mismatches. Within weeks,
our agents cut their order processing time
by 70 % in eliminated stockouts entirely.
Real client, real results, scale your business,
not your workload. Get your free discovery
audit at Rizflow .co.